A threat to Superman is a threat to society.
Injustice is a animation, science fiction, fantasy film directed by Matt Peters.
When Lois Lane is killed, an unhinged Superman
decides to take control of the Earth.
Determined to stop him, Batman creates a team of freedom-fighting heroes.
But when superheroes go to war, can the world survive?
Clark Kent / Superman / Kal-El (voice), played by Justin Hartley.
Bruce Wayne / Batman (voice), played by Anson Mount.
Lois Lane / Rama Kushna (voice), played by Laura Bailey.
Diana Prince / Wonder Woman (voice), played by Janet Varney.
Damian Wayne / Robin / Jimmy Olsen (voice), played by Zach Callison.
Selina Kyle / Catwoman (voice), played by Anika Noni Rose.
Injustice is a 2021 American adult animated superhero film based on the prequel comic series of the 2013
NetherRealm Studios video game Injustice: Gods Among Us, and based on characters from DC Comics.
Produced by Warner Bros.
Animation and DC Entertainment, and distributed by Warner Bros.
Home Entertainment, it is the 47th installment in the DC
Universe Animated Original Movies line.
The film is directed by Matt Peters from a story by Ernie Altbacker and stars
Justin Hartley and Anson Mount as Superman and Batman, respectively.
The film, set in a separate continuity from the main DC Universe, follows Superman’s descent into madness after being tricked
by Joker into killing his pregnant wife Lois Lane and detonating a nuclear weapon that destroys Metropolis.
As Superman transforms the Earth into a police state to enforce global peace, Batman
forms an underground resistance to oppose Superman and his allies.
The film was announced in May 2021, with Altbacker writing the script.
The film adapts elements from both the Injustice video game and its prequel comic book series (primarily
the Year One arc), but tells an original narrative which diverges from the source materials.
The film explores themes of superhero, based on comic, based on video game.
The tone is thought_provoking.